Technical Product Manager

Tactical and strategic technology professional with software engineering, product, and business development successes. Responsible for growing new customer revenue and building innovative products across diverse roles such as product manager for a virtual reality startup creating brand metaverse experiences, developer for a leading healthcare legal consulting firm, marketing coordinator for a \$250M+ rev/year retailer, and partner eco-system management.

Professional portfolio includes advertisements that are seen by millions monthly and SaaS solutions delivering millions in ARR. Recent organizational impacts include tripling prospect to client conversion rate, increasing product offerings 100%, and 90%+ SaaS client retention.

Experience

Product Manager @ Obsess May 2022 - June 2023, New York, New York
 Led technical projects improving core SaaS product features and data management platform. Launched top performing marketing campaigns featuring A-List celebrities for global brands
Consultant & Developer @ Manatt August 2017 - April 2022, New York, New York
Presented AI healthcare and legal analysis at Google Cloud Next, saving consultant time an improving platform content variety.
☐ Technical expertise for SaaS from launch through \$1MM+/ARR. ☐ Equipped editorial board with content performance analysis, guiding content investment.
Partner Development @ Arkadium July 2016 - April 2017, New York, New York
 Signed 25+ strategic partnerships, including: Top tier publishers reaching over 20MM visits/mo. 100% new revenue for Artificial Intelligence platform.
 Responsible for new business development and assigned all inbound leads. Fastest sales growth within company records.
Consultant @ Marketing Systems November 2015 - January 2018, Dallas, Texas
□ Influencer campaign with a Team USA athlete driving 10K+ organic video views in 3 days. □ Created models to track millions of daily impressions and aligned brand across digital.
Digital Sales Executive @ YP June 2015 - November 2015, Dallas, Texas
□ Used Salesforce to maintain \$2M ARR pipeline for SEM and mobile media. □ Created unique mobile product mix for non-profit and brand fundraising/e-commerce. □ Innovated on prospect pitch process for 50+ regional sales team.
Marketing Campaign Manager @ Texas Print May 2014 - June 2015, Dallas, Texas
☐ Created new product business model for B2B clients. ☐ Developed HTML5 landing page + marketing campaign for e-commerce launch. ☐ Enabled team of 8 to specialize by creating a digital inventory management.
Marketing Coordinator @ Goody Goody May 2013 - June 2013, Dallas, Texas
□ Led corporate marketing for 20+ retail stores within Texas. □ Coordinated \$25k/monthly creative in print, digital, and radio. ○ Saved \$50,000 shopping out an OOH vendor. ○ Saved 10% on \$1MM+ print budget by managing placements.

Education

B.S. in Marketing @ University of Texas at Dallas August 2010 - December 2013